stanzoopages.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Stanzoopages.com

##  Privacy Policy

Stanzoo, one of the leading local search engines is an expressive source for those who are in search of accurate and valid information pertaining to any product or service in their respective locations. To avail the information, one needs to get registered and surf through the business lists or yellow pages in Stanzoo website. You can also list your business or service thus, to benefit yourself as well as Stanzoo. 

While registering to avail various services of our leading local search engine [www.stanzoopages.com](http://www.stanzoopages.com/) , either through online business directory or for free SMS registration, you may be required to give your name, residence address, email address, date of birth and similar Personal Information. 

We are committed to protect the confidentiality and privacy of all personal information given to us in order to maintain your safety thus, safeguarding our Organisation’s reliability. We enrich this policy in demonstrating good business growth. 

We collect the personal information about our visitors, which will be used by us for the following purposes: completion and support of the current activity, website and system administration, and research and development. 

We as a firm, assures you that we do not share, sell or rent Personal Information except to reach our customers while informing them about our new practices. Personal Information we collect shall be shared with our subscribers/advertisers and you shall be deemed to have given consent to the same. 

We will share Personal Information only under one or more of the following circumstances: \- If we have your consent or deemed consent to do so - If we are compelled by law (including court orders) to do so. 

You are eligible to edit your account information irrespective of time. In strengthening the security and privacy, we are deemed to take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services offered on our website if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don’t provide information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the our services. 

If you are our corporate customer, it is possible that we have entered into a contract with you for non-disclosure of confidential information. This Policy shall not affect such a contract in any manner. 

**Questions:** If you have any questions or complaints relating to this Privacy Policy or how we use the personal information we have about you, please do not hesitate in contacting us. We assure you of prompt response.
